C

Max Fell

Max Fell

5622 SE Cable Dr, 34997, Stuart, FL Stuart, FL 34997 772-291-8316

Maxwilliamfell@gmail.com

Skills

- Guest Relations
- Event Planning
- Customer Service
- Quality assurance
- Problem Resolution
- Data evaluation
- Cash handling accuracy
- Relationship selling
- Reliable and punctual
- Energetic self-starter
- Outgoing personality
- Excellent communication skills
- Team player mentality
- Negotiations
- Developing client relations over multiple visits
- Serving effectively, with a smile!
- Dedicated to making the customer and company happy at the same time!

Education

- High School
- UCF Full Stack Software Development Certificate

Summary

Personable and dedicated Customer Service Representative with extensive experience in the service industry. Solid team player with upbeat, positive attitude and proven skills int establishing rapport with clients. Motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and contribute to company success. Specialize in quality, speed and process optimization. Articulate, enthusiastic and results-oriented with demonstrated passion for building relationships, cultivating partnerships and growing businesses

EXPERIENCE

Host

Stuart, Florida

Galaxy Diner/Nov 2019 to Mar 2020

- Supported serving staff, food runners and bussers to keep the dining room presentable and ready for guests.
- Supported management by resolving customer service and food-related issues to maintain guest satisfaction.
- Managed daily card and cash transactions by maintaining payment records and investigating irregularities.

Waiters Assistant

Stuart, FL

District Table Bar and Grill/Jun 2018 to Jul 2019

- Cleared tables efficiently to maintain high turnover rate and minimize wait times.
- Greeted guests with friendliness and professionalism.
- Supported serving staff in delivering accurate and well-presented food orders.
- Applied proactive and resourceful nature to create pleasant guest experiences.
- Maintained knowledge of menu items, garnishes, ingredients and preparation methods to assist guests with menu selection.
- Suggested additional items and offered samples of weekly promotional items to increase store sales.

Waiter Stuart, FL

Mariner Sands Oct 2020-

- Served club members proficiently
- Served numerous tables at once
- Helpful to other servers that might need assistance
- Exceeded management expectations go provide guests with the best possible experience.
- Fast, clear minded service to minimize mistakes.
- Used to going above and beyond doing whatever needs to be done.
- Built ongoing relationships with members and created friendships while selling goods and products.

Helper Stuart, FL

European Auto Performance Sep 2021-

- Learning more and more about developing customer relations.
- Learning how to solve complex equations including multiple different possible solutions or problems.
- Learning and helping the staff with vigorous and time consuming tasks.

Waiter

Palm beach gardens

Carmine's la trattoria October 2021- February 2022

- Greeting guests, introducing myself, offering wine cocktails, or water.
- Keeping the work environment clean, while not alerting guests of a mess.

Valet

Stuart, fl

Johnson Honda

- Greet customers, make them aware of wait times, make service advisors aware of appointments.
- Keep the drive clean and prepared
- Stock snacks and drinks for guests
- Check guests tire pressure and alignment